A website does not have to be broken to fail you.
It can work exactly as its owner designed it.
And still omit the feature your life depends on.
OpenPatch is a public feature layer for websites users do not control.
MetroCare is a credible twelve-provider directory.
But there is no search, combined filtering, or comparison.
To find wheelchair access, Urdu, and new patients,
you must inspect every card yourself.
OpenPatch creates a privacy-safe Repair Brief
with bounded structural signals for Codex.
Field values, cookies, storage, query strings,
and page text never enter the brief.
GPT-5.6 through Codex inspects the DOM and screenshots,
defines acceptance criteria, and chooses constrained operations.
It cannot provide JavaScript, HTML, callbacks, fetches,
cookies, templates, or arbitrary page-text extraction.
Now the exact constrained runtime is active.
Eleven of eleven operations are healthy.
Two providers become a keyboard-accessible comparison table
built only from declared data attributes.
Wheelchair access, Urdu, and accepting new patients
reduce twelve services to one understandable choice.
Preferences stay local, results are announced,
and our browser test proves the interactions emit zero requests.
The extension discovers the community feature automatically
and shows scope, permissions, integrity, and compatibility.
One click installs it. Everyone downstream needs
no AI, account, or API key.
The Compatibility Sentinel checks every published target
in Chromium every six hours.
If the original site changes, the patch is quarantined
before another user discovers it.
Built in this primary GPT-5.6 and Codex thread:
40 unit tests, 14 browser journeys, and 4 extension tests.
When a site will not add the feature people need, users still can.
Fix the web you have.