Patch the Web is a safe repair layer for websites you don't own.
Let me show you the complete flow: downloading the real extension, finding a community fix, and turning a frustrating site into something genuinely useful.
I'm downloading the extension from our public site and opening Chrome's extension page.
For this demo it's loaded unpacked, exactly like a judge can install it from the release.
Using community repairs needs no account and no API key.
Here is MetroCare before the repair.
It lists twelve services, but there is no search, no accessibility filter, and no way to compare providers.
Finding wheelchair-accessible care in your language means reading every card.
When I open Patch the Web, it finds a community repair written for this exact page.
Before showing Install, the extension checks the publisher policy, the patch's cryptographic hash, and all eleven selectors against the live website.
Now I install it.
The repair is a constrained data document, never arbitrary JavaScript.
Every operation is allow-listed, every selector was preflighted, and the permission applies only to this website.
The page now has the feature its owner never built.
I can select two real listings and open a keyboard-accessible comparison, while the original site stays intact underneath the repair layer.
Now I'll filter for wheelchair access, Urdu, and providers accepting new patients.
Twelve cards become one useful result.
Those preferences stay inside this browser; neither MetroCare nor Patch the Web receives them.
I'll reload the website.
The repair runs again automatically, and my unfinished filter choices are still here.
This is a durable browser feature, not a screenshot and not a one-time AI preview.
The extension shows exactly what's active, where it can run, and whether every operation is still healthy.
Permissions remain reviewable, and the user can disable the repair whenever they want.
Codex and GPT-5.6 accelerated the hard part: inspecting DOM and screenshot evidence, authoring the constrained patch, threat-modeling it, and running browser tests.
Everyone else simply installs the verified result.
That's Patch the Web: users fixing the web together.